smartcanucks.ca 2019-06-30

# SmartCanucks Privacy Policy | Canadian Freebies, Coupons, Deals, Bargains, Flyers, Contests Canada

For each unregistered/non-member visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or their e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail storing information volunteered by members, such as survey information and site registrations.

We do not share, sell or rent your email address, postal address or any other data we hold about you to any third party.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages, used to customize the content of our page individual visitor’s and to provide accounting for our cashback rebates with our retail partners who you may choose to purchase from.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access and also to track what great canadian cashback rebates are due to you from your purchases with our retail partners.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by contacting us via our contact form.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, including unique identifier information (e.g., member number and password), transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) and contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number).

Members can access this information by emailing or mailing us.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the following addresses:

**SmartCanucks  
34 Eglinton Ave West, Suite 149  
Toronto, ON, M4R 2H6  
**

## Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at contact@smartcanucks.ca and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behaviour using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)
